Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Records, 1750-2014 and undated RL.10159
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Exhibits, events, and projects, 1908-2012 and undated; 2; 9.7 Linear Feet; 36.8 Gigabytes
  - Other exhibits, events, and projects, 1908-2011 and undated; 2
    - Ucko Exhibition - Reception Finances, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Ucko Exhibit - related articles, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Text Panel/Drafts Storyboards, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - What We Brought With Us, Returned Loan Objects, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - [Comments - What We Brought With Us], 1997 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - [Exhibit - What We Brought With Us: Mementos of the Flight From Europe 1933 to 1950], 1998 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Permanent Exhibit "What We Brought With Us", 1998 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Photographs and negatives - "What We Brought With Us", 1998 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - [Photographs - What We Brought With Us Exhibit], 1998 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Subject files, 1750-2014 and undated; 3; 18.3 Linear Feet; 544.2 Megabytes
  The Subject files series contains materials collected by JHFNC historian Leonard Rogoff that are primarily related to his research for various JHFNC projects and personal interests including "Down Home," "Migrations," Southern Jewish identity, North Carolina synagogues, temples, and congregations, and the history of the Durham-Chapel Hill Jewish community.
  The materials in this series are arranged into two subseries: North Carolina municipalities and Topical subject files.
  - North Carolina municipalities, 1827-2013 and undated; 3
    The primary focuses of the materials in this subseries are on the Jewish families and communities in various North Carolina cities, towns, and villages. The contents include clippings, articles, obituaries, newsletters, and individual, family, and synagogue and temple histories. Also included are primary manuscript materials, transcripts from oral histories, and photographs.
    The folders in this subseries are arranged loosely in alphabetical order, reflecting the original order of the materials.
    Digital photographs and other files related to North Carolina municipalities are located in the Exhibits, Events, and Projects series and are arranged by the project they were associated with.
    - Lipsitz - Ahoskie, Windsor, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Angier, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Apex, 2005 and undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Asheville, 1978, 1997-2008; 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Asheville, 1978, 1997-2008; 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Asheville Beth HaTephila, 1896-2010, predominant 1933-1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Asheville - Beth HaTephila - Rabbi Unger, 1950-1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Asheville - Dave, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Asheville - Finkelstein, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Asheville - Karpen, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Asheville - Michalove, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Asheville - Pollock, 1949, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Asheville - Straus, 1970-1971, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Asheville - Sternberg, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Asheville - Winner, 1933, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Asheville - Ladies Aid, 1916, 1927, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Asheville - UNC-Asheville, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Asheville - Bikur Cholim/Beth Israel, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - [Asheville - oral histories], 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - [Photographs - Asheville], 2010 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Beaufort, 1803, 1987 and undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - [Photographs - Beaufort], undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Benson, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Bethania, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Black Mtn, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Boone, 1987, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - App State, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Brevard, 2003-2010; 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Brevard, 2003-2010; 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Burlington - Levin, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Burnsville/Penland, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Candor, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Carrboro, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Cary, 1998-2010 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Chapel Hill Synagogue, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Chapel Hill Kehillah, 1996-2009 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Kehillah Dissolution, 1999-2004 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Chapel Hill Kehillah Memorial Book, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - [Kehillah Multi-Minyan], 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Kehillah School, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah Budget], 2001-2006 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - [Kehillah Board], 2002, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah Membership], 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah], 2002-2004; 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah], 2002-2004; 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah miscellaneous], 2002-2008 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Kehillah Mission Statement, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Kehillah - B'nai Mitzvah, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - [Chapel Hill Kehillah Bylaws], 2004 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - [Kashrut at the Kehillah], undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Chapel Hill - Strauss, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Chapel Hill - Etz Hayim, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Chapel Hill - Elion, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Chapel Hill, 1998-2009; 1 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Chapel Hill, 1998-2009; 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Chapel Hill, 1998-2009; 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Chapel Hill], 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte - Blumenthal, 1997-2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Charlotte - Cohen, Drucker, 1858, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Charlotte - Cohen, 1845-2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Charlotte - Levine, 1980-2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Charlotte - Davidson (Schiff), 1892, 1979, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Charlotte - Klein, 1968, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Charlotte - Lebo/Silverstein, 1982, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Charlotte - Gorelick, 2002, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Charlotte - Schiff Family, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Charlotte - Speizman, 1987, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Charlotte - Wittkowsky, 1931, 1995 and undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Charlotte - CAJE (Carolina Agency for Jewish Education), 1988-1993, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Charlotte - Amity Club, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Charlotte, 1910-1982, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Charlotte - LMNS (Levine Museum of the New South), 1992, 2002 and undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Charlotte Jewish History Society, 2005, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Charlotte - Shalom Park, 1994, 2004-2008 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Charlotte - Push, Pluck, Perseverance, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Charlotte Cemetery, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Charlotte - Temple Israel, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Charlotte - Schindler, 2008 and undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Charlotte - Schloss (Baer, Silverman), 1985, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Charlotte oral history, 1992-1993, 1996-1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Charlotte - Temple Israel oral history, circa 1990-1998; 1 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Charlotte - Temple Israel oral history, circa 1990-1998; 2 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte - Temple Israel oral history, circa 1990-1998; 3 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Charlotte], 1909, 1993, 2001, 2010 and undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Clinton, 1982, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Photographs - Clinton], 1953 and undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Cullowhee, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Concord, 2004-2009 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Dunn - Baer, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Dunn, 1918, 1959, 1969, 1994-2008 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - [35 mm slides - Dunn], 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Durham - CH JCC, 2008-2012 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - [Jewish Federation Durham-Chapel Hill Brochures], 2002-2011 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Community Midrasha [Jewish Federation of Durham/Chapel Hill], 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 1 of 6 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 2 of 6 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 3 of 6 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 4 of 6 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 5 of 6 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Durham, 1866-2012, bulk 1999-2012; 6 of 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Durham, 1866-1915, 1940-2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Durham - Evans, 1997-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Durham - Goldgar, 2004 and undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Durham/Burlington - Goldman, 2002, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Durham - Judea Reform, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - [Judea Reform Congregation/Rabbi Efraim Rosenzweig], 1946-2003; 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - [Judea Reform Congregation/Rabbi Efraim Rosenzweig], 1946-2003; 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Durham - Margolis, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Durham - Meyers, 1999, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - [Durham/Chapel Hill oral history notes], 1986 and undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Durham], 1924-2000 and undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Eden, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Edenton, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Elizabeth City, 1858, 1924, 1977, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - [Photographs - Elizabeth City], undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Ham - Anti-Semitism, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Saunders - Book of Ham, 1934, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Elizabethtown, 1977, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Elizabethtown - Leinwards, 1992-1993, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - [Photographs - Elizabethtown], 1956 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Elon University, 2005, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Enfield, 1898, 1936, and undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - [Photographs - Enfield], undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Baer/Moff, 1940-1963, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Baer, 1942, 1954, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Bloom, 1910, 1925, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Fayetteville - Families, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Fayetteville - Evans, 1999, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Fayetteville - Fleishman, 1944-2006 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Fayetteville - Stein, 1931-1945, 1960-1980, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Fayetteville, 2000-2001, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Fayetteville - Beth Israel, 1969, 1997-2009 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Fort Bragg, 1968, 2000, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Fayetteville], 1969, 2000-2001 and undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Franklin, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Franklinton, 1961, 1966, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Gastonia, 1938, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Gastonia - Rauch, 1967-1970, 2004-2006 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Goldsboro, 1878-1939, 1977-2008 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Goldsboro - Susman, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - [Photographs - Goldsboro], 1997 and undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Greensboro - Loewenstein, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Sidney Stern/Greensboro NC B'nai B'rith, 1872, 1879, 1920-1948, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Greensboro - Arthur Joan Bluetenthal, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Greensboro - Family History - Cone, 1928-1947, 1979, 2002-2007 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Greensboro - Marks, 2000, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - [Greensboro - Meyer/Cohen/Harris], 1886, 1897, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Greensboro - Klein, 1946, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Greensboro - Rypins, 1938-1957, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Greensboro - Family History - Oetlinger/Stern/Weinberg, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Greensboro - LeBauer, 1977, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Greensboro - Samet, 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Greensboro - Schiffmann, 1952, 1955, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Greensboro - Sloan, 1985, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Greensboro - Sternberger - Benjamin - Tannenbaum, 1924, 1964, 1988, 2003-2008 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Greensboro - Tanger, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Articles - Newspaper, Identity, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Greensboro - Beth David [Synagogue], 1947, 1969, 2004, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Greensboro Reformed Hebrew Cong, 1908-1925 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Greensboro - Temple Emanuel, 1912-2008 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Greensboro - Temple Emanuel talk, 2007 and undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Greensboro City History, 1932, 1943, 1982, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Greensboro, 1836, 1906-1987, 2002-2009; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Greensboro, 1836, 1906-1987, 2002-2010; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Greensboro History - Horowitz, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - [Photographs - Greensboro], 1920s, 1951-2010; 1 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - [Photographs - Greensboro], 1920s, 1951-2010; 2 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - [Photographs - Greensboro], 1920s, 1951-2010; 3 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Greenville, 1994, 2000-2011 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Greenville - Brody, 1990, 1999, 2008-2011 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - [Photographs - Greenville], 1992 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Halifax, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Henderson, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Hendersonville - Beryl Cohen, 1920, 1922, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Hendersonville, 1920-1927, 1951, 1983-2008 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - [Photographs - Hendersonville], undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Hickory - Zerden, 1926-2009 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Hickory, 1938, 2002-2007 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - [Photographs - Hickory], undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - High Point - Bernard, 1970 and undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - High Point - Kaplan - Greensboro/High Pt/Raleigh, 1911-1925, 2005-2008 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - High Point - Kiel, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - High Point - Samet, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - High Point, 1919, 1926-2008; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - High Point, 1919, 1926-2008; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - High Point - Swartzberg, 1958, 1965, 1970, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - High Point - Rabbi Peres, 1911-1916, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - High Point Naturalization, 1894, 1897, 1906 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - [Photographs - High Point], undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Hillsborough, 1866, 2005, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Hillsborough - Sexias, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Jacksonville - Popkin, 1977, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Jacksonville, 1960, 1997-2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Kinston - Schechter, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kinston, 1913-2008 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Kinston - Pearson, 1923, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Kinston - Kanter/Bloom, 2005, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Kinston - Goode/Goodkowitz, 1915-2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Kinston - Oettinger, 2005 and undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Kinston - Pearson, 1910-1913, 1999; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Kinston - Pearson, 1910-1913, 1999; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Kinston], circa 1900s, 1999 and undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Kitty Hawk - Jewish Community Outer Banks, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Lexington, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Lake Norman, 2006, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Lenoir, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Lincolnton, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Littleton, 1881 and undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Louisburg, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Lumberton - Weinstein, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Lumberton - Lasting Impressions, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Lumberton, 1903-2008 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - [Photographs - Lumberton], 1982 and undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Marion, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Mebane, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mooresville, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Morehead City, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Mt. Airy, 1910, 1998, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Mt. Airy/Raleigh - Schafer, 1917, 1944, 1967-2005 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - [Photograph - Mt. Airy], circa 1900s (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Murphy - Elias, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - New Bern/Gastonia - Hahn, 1880s-1946, 2006-2008 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - New Bern - Temple Chester B'nai Sholem, 1894, 1914, 1972-1976, 2004-2006 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - New Bern - Lipman, 1894, 1916-1920, 1995-2007 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - New Bern - Coplon/Lipman/Howard/Orringer, 2000-2006 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - New Bern - Nathan, 1787, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - New Bern Cemetery, 1790-1809, 2008-2011 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - New Bern, 1790-1924, 1959, 1987-2008 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - [Photographs - New Bern], circa 1900s, 1958 and undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Oxford - Munich, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Oxford - Fox, 2006, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Oxford, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Pinehurst, 1985, 2005-2008 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Pittsboro, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Raeford, 1961, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Raleigh - Ehrlich, 1981, 2003, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Raleigh - Grausman/Elias/Auerbach, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Raleigh - Holtzman, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - [Raleigh], 1916, 1989, 2008-2013 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Raleigh, 1892-1916, 1982-2009; 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Raleigh, 1892-1916, 1982-2009; 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Raleigh, 1892-1916, 1982-2009; 3 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Raleigh - Beth Meyer, 1977, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Raleigh - Schoen, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Raleigh - Satisky, 2006, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Raleigh - Sherbondy, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Raleigh WWII - David Glass, 1941-1947 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - [Raleigh Shul community], 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - [Photograph and 35 mm slides - Raleigh], 1915-1928, 2003 and undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke Rapids, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - [Photographs - Roanoke Rapids], undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Robbins, 1943-2007 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Rockingham, 1877, 1916, 1946, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Rocky Mount, 1949-2008 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - [Photographs - Rocky Mount], 1981-1988 and undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Rosman, 1932, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Rougemont, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - St Paul's, 1982, 1988 and undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Salisbury, 1997, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Scotland Neck, 1989, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - [Photograph - Scotland Neck], undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Siler City, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Snow Camp, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Snow Hill, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Southern Pines, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Statesville - Temple Emanuel, 1989, 1992, 2003-2007 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Statesville, 1884, 1988-2007 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Statesville - Gordon, 1997, 2000-2008 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Statesville - Wallace, 1895-2009 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - [Photographs - Statesville], undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Swansboro, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Sylva, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Sylva - Sol Schulman, 1992, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - [Photographs - Sylva], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Tarboro, 1869-2004; 1 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Tarboro, 1869-2004; 2 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Tarboro, 1869-2004; 3 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Tarboro - Sternglanz - Holocaust, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Tarboro], 1945, 1999 and undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Taylorsville, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Van Eden, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Wallace, 1951, 1972-2009 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Warrenton - Mordecai, 1827, 2002, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Warrenton - Katzenstein, 1899, 1940-2007 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Warrenton - Diamond/Perman/Friedenberg, 1993, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Warrenton], 2000 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Warsaw, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Washington, 1972, 1995, 1999, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Weldon, 1954, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Weldon - Freid, 1979, 2001-2009 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Weldon - Kittner, 1915, 1967-1970, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Whiteville, 1861-1881, 1934-1999 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - [Photographs - Whiteville], undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Whitakers - Bloom Store, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Williamston - Margolis, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Williamston, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Williamston - Needleman, 1925-1926. 2005 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Wilmington - Hebrew Cemetery, 1855, 1860, 1987, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Wilmington - Bear, 1938, 1992; 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Wilmington - Bear, 1938, 1992; 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Wilmington - Mendelsohn, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Wilmington - Arthur Miller, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Wilmington - Block, 1942, 1991-2008 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Wilmington - Blumenthal, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Wilmington - Einstein, 1900-1930, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Wilmington - Finkelstein, 1913 and undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Wilmington - Fishblate, 1898, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Wilmington - D'Lugin, 1919-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Wilmington - Jacobi, 1979, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Wilmington - Schwartz, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Wilmington - Schloss, 1992, 1996. 2009 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Wilmington - Warshaeuer Miller, 1992-1997, 2002, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Wilmington - Weill, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Wilmington Genealogy, 2010 and undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Wilmington - Temple of Israel, 1875, 1971, 1998-2010 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Wilmington [?] - Bill Reaves, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Wilmington - Goldberg, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Wilmington - Histories, 1860, 1918-2008 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Wilmington - B'nai Israel, 1898, 1966-2009; 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Wilmington - B'nai Israel, 1898, 1966-2009; 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Wilmington data, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Wilmington - Hieke, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Wilmington Jewry- Sims, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Wilmington - Race riot, 1898, 1984-2011 and undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Wilmington - UNC - W, 1904, 1990, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Kelley's Wilmington Directory, 1860-1861 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Wilmington], 2000 and undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Wilson - Leder, 1949-1951, 1991-2007 and undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Wilson - Joseph Hanchrow, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, 1979, 1995-2009 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Wilson], 1907, 1918, 1942, 1967-1999 and undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Windsor, 2005, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Winston-Salem, 1938-2007 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Winston-Salem - B'nai B'rith, 1944, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Winston-Salem - Temple Emanuel Booklet, 1927-1931, 1944, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Winston-Salem - Temple Emanuel, 1932-1963 and undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Winston-Salem - Libby Holman, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Winston-Salem - Brenner, 1973-2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - [Photographs - Winston-Salem], circa 1900s and undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Yanceyville, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Zebulon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Topical subject files, 1750-2014 and undated; 4
    The topics in this subseries vary widely but primarily focus on North Carolina and southern Jewish history from the early 1800s to the present. The contents include clippings, articles, newsletters, photocopied research papers and manuscript materials; excerpts from books, family genealogies and histories, and other printed materials; photographs; and some of Rogoff's research-related correspondence, handwritten notes, bibliographies, outlines, and typed speeches on various topics.